Okay, very important here, module two, campus resources.
A lot of college students, not even just first generation college students, but college students general do not utilize campus resources.
I didn't at first until I realized all the different resources that we had for free and it's included in your package.
And for, you know, this one, the objective is locate and describe the function at least five major campus resources and I am confident your campus, your college campus will have those five major resources.
Explain how to access these resources, identify which resources address which problems and build a personal resource map.
I didn't really know about a lot of resources campus health extremely important, the writing center or academic study center whatever your college has for for all that career services center very important to get your LinkedIn down to get your resume down.
And then many more I used to do a work study at student wellness, and we didn't really see many, many students, but it talks about you know student health student wellness.
There are plenty of resources that you can find on your college campus and, and I think it's extremely important to navigate through these resources, you know financial aid, a resource, extremely important counseling, very important if you're, you know, college is not going to be the easiest time for you
to go into that a lot more in the later modules, disability services, accommodations, food pantry, if you're ever facing food insecurity every college, or at least UNC and I'm pretty sure a lot of other colleges have these resources tutoring centers.
They're included the free. Make sure that you go into, you know, your campus map your campus, your school website, and then go do this exercise at my school. This resources, this resource is located at wherever and take note of it.
And you'll never know when you might need a resource down the line. You might think, as I did freshman year, I don't need these resources. Why would I need to go to, you know, a career center or student wellness.
And, you know, I had to learn the hard way why I might have me to do that. So make sure you go thoroughly do this module, take down any notes, read the lessons, do the activities, and you might surprise yourself about what resources your college campus may have.